Morning, Tomaki!
Morning to you, Sahara.
I'll be back later.
Take care of the house for me, will ya?
Yes, Master. Of course I will.
Where are you going?
To school.
Summer vacation's over, so we have to go back to class.
Oh, yeah?
Listen, I'm only gonna tell you this once.
Do not follow me.
I won't.
Come on, will ya? We don't want to be late.
Coming. See you later.
So long, Master.
So, did you do yesterday's modern language homework?
It was really hard.
No. Can I copy yours?
Maybe. What are you gonna do for me?
Well, that's good.
See, you wanna go check out this school business?
But I promised Master I would take care of the house.
For crying out loud, just give me that!
I can hear my heart.
I'll probably see you later.
Okay.
The beginning was the time
You were suddenly suddenly
You were suddenly born
You were born in the first place
You were the one who was born
It's true that you are
o
and Yerbo
yeah
I ain't
really
It's true that you have to learn
I can anything
What is our connection
You have to feel the joy
You can arrive
A way of触れる
Thank you.
Why has humanity always been so entranced by the sky?
In Greek mythology, there's a short tale that demonstrates this.
To escape their island prison, a man fashioned wings of wax and feathers for himself and his son.
The man warned his son to follow close behind, but lost in the euphoria of flight, the boy soared too close to the sun.
His wings melted and he fell to his death in the sea.
This body of water was eventually named after the boy.
Icarus.
Yes.
There's no need to respond.
I'm sorry.
All humans should be able to fly like an avian on wings that no one can see.
It's a travesty we can't.
What is Icarus doing here at school?
We have a couple new transfer students joining us today.
This is Icarus and Nymph.
Please welcome them to our class.
I don't believe this.
What are they doing here?
It's so hot.
Are you all right, Master?
Wait, she knows Tomaki?
Oh man, they're both totally cute.
It looks like they're both wearing wings.
I didn't know Tomaki was into that sort of thing.
Toma, what should we do?
If I put up a stink now, everyone will find out I know these freaky aliens.
Come on, Tomaki.
Calm your nerves.
Peace and quiet is the best.
What the hell are you two doing here?
Sorry, Master.
Nymph made me.
I see no problem with us going to school.
Sure, now it's just going to school.
What's the next headache you'll cause?
Don't get your panties in a wad.
I mean, really, how is this a bad thing?
Maybe try going with it.
It'll certainly make your life more interesting.
I'm pretty freaking sure my life is interesting enough.
Perhaps it is.
What's that mean?
Oh, that's so adorable.
You have little sleeves for your wings sewn into your uniform.
Dammit, listen to what I'm saying, you jerk-offs.
How are you a transfer student when you've never set foot in a school?
I helped myself to one of Alpha's cards
and made some adjustments to your teacher's memory.
Who the hell does that?
Take a few deep breaths, Tomaki.
Chill.
Now listen, because this is important.
Don't you think you should let them adjust
to a normal way of life?
You are always telling Icarus to act more like a human being,
so where's the harm in her trying?
He has a point.
And let's not forget about Nymph here.
She needs to learn about the world, too, you know.
Just look at Icarus.
She's like a doll with a face molded into a frown.
Don't you want to step up and help her?
Yeah, all right, I get it.
Promise you'll act normal and not do anything crazy?
Don't have to tell me, dumb bug.
Nymph, Icarus, this is great news.
You'll have so much fun.
Get ready for the time of your lives.
I'm going to show you what being in school is really about.
Okay.
This is the continent of Australia.
It's very big, so it has a number of different climate zones.
Hey, Icarus, how's it going?
Are you having any issues taking notes?
I'm pretty good at it, so I can make copies for you if you...
Oh, well, I guess Icarus can copy off the board just fine by herself.
That's good.
I'm proud of her.
Uh-huh.
Wait.
Nymph hasn't been here nearly as long as Icarus has.
I bet I can teach her all sorts of stuff.
Hey, Nymph, aren't you taking notes?
If you want, you can totally copy off of mine.
Doesn't matter.
Okay.
Just thought I'd offer.
So what are you looking at out the window?
The birds.
You like birds, huh?
Me too.
I can even tell you what each of them is called.
That one right there is called a tree sparrow,
and that one is a...
It's a pied wagtail, right?
Over there's a white eye, another wagtail,
and the chubby one's a great tit.
There's an oriental turtle dove,
a white-cheeked starling, and a bulbul.
Uh-uh.
Today we'll be focusing on cooking.
Everyone split into groups and cook whatever you like.
Just make sure you have fun.
Okay.
All right.
I'm pretty awesome at home heck.
This time, I'll be able to give Icarus and Nymph tons of advice.
Here, let me help you, Icarus.
You gotta make sure and hold the knife right, like this.
Check this out, Nymph.
To bring out the flavor and add some pizzazz to your dish, use soy sauce.
It's yummy.
Amazing.
Thank you so much, Zohara.
Oh yeah, I'm all over this.
Miss Tadai?
I noticed Icarus and Nymph aren't here yet.
Shouldn't we wait for them?
Sorry, we're late.
Why am I holding this stupid fish?
I'm sorry, Nymph.
I needed help.
I couldn't carry both of them.
Well, I guess we better start cooking, huh?
Wow, Icarus, that's so awesome.
Just like a real chef.
That's amazing.
That's good.
I think I have a sweet tooth.
Quit it.
We're not supposed to eat them yet.
Shut up, whiner bug.
Are you cooking or just tasting everyone else's?
That's mine.
You can't have that much smoke inside.
Oh man, what a mess.
So, Nymph, you just transferred here?
Was your last school so far ahead of us academically
that you feel it's all right to ignore every word I'm saying?
That's it.
If you want to daydream, then solve this problem first.
No problem.
A 12-sided polygon is drawn inside a circle
which has a radius of one.
The length of a single side of said...
What in the world is Nymph talking about?
I don't even understand the problem, let alone the answer.
Icarus, do you understand this?
I don't think any of us students are actually going to the right...
Me neither.
I am so lost.
Since you're so put to interrupt the class like that,
then answer this next question.
Who, me?
I don't know if I...
Icarus, take it easy there.
If X equals X squared minus NX plus M,
therefore, the equation for the axis would be
X equals positive N over 2.
Because N is less than or equal to 2M,
then X will be...
Manzana.
Manzana?
Hey, Alpha.
What are you thinking about right now?
Oh, I just got some juicy information.
It looks like bringing you to school is worth the trouble after all.
So, how did your morning classes go?
Freakin' awful.
But Nymph and Icarus are good students,
which surprised me since they're angeloids and all.
How are they doing socially?
Any trouble fitting in?
Judging by the way the boys are fawning over them,
I'd say they're adjusting pretty well.
You see?
Huh?
When did this happen?
The entire school's talking about the two cute transfer girls.
Sure didn't take very long for the news to spread.
This is insane.
Listen up, you disgusting bugs!
Keep the chatter down!
I'm trying to watch myself!
And now, just like bugs, watch them scatter.
Ooh!
Freakless, baby, we're bad boys!
Hey, what happened to Zohara?
Take a look for yourself.
You okay?
Leave me alone!
Let me guess.
You've been comparing yourself to them all day,
and now you feel like a big fat ugly loser.
Oops, did I hit a nerve?
Enough, Mikiko.
You're being rude.
Uh-oh.
Time for our next class.
What?
We have to go to more classes?
But they're all so boring!
Damn it!
The Alpha!
Help me!
Get your filthy hands off of me!
You should be shamed of yourself!
Sunday!
Today, class, we will be learning about chemical symbols and formulae.
Life is so wonderful!
Oh, yeah, baby!
I'm a vegan for life, that's for sure!
I would like to do things a little differently.
A guest lecturer will be taking over the class.
Here.
I'd like you to meet Miss Icarus.
Hello, class.
What the hell?
She's teaching us now?
Oh, wow.
She looks great in a lab coat.
You put her up to the stick, didn't you?
Ooh, she'll be a great teacher.
I could listen to Icarus drone on for hours.
She's like the smartest person I've ever known!
I'll start as soon as everyone's ready.
That's not the problem!
Miss Icarus, can you tell us what we'll be studying today?
Wait a minute!
What are you doing here?
Teacher!
I propose we use Tomuki as a test subject for some fun experiments.
Don't treat me like your plaything!
You don't own me!
Nobody owns me!
This is our subject for today.
Let's begin with a demonstration.
Any volunteers?
What do you mean, volunteers?
Don't look at me!
Let go of me!
You're abusing my rights or something!
Don't worry.
You'll be fine.
Many people have wings on their backs,
although they are invisible to the naked human eye.
They are there.
And, Master, your wings are much larger than most.
I'm sure of it.
I don't know why exactly, but I am.
Go on, Master.
The sky is calling to you.
Tomo King!
I was prepared for this eventuality.
These are for you, Tomoki.
Thanks for looking out, bro.
That is so awesome!
Fly, Tomoki, fly!
You can do it. We believe in you.
Do it for us!
Tomoki! Tomoki! Tomoki! Tomoki! Tomoki! Tomoki! Tomoki! Tomoki! Tomoki! Tomoki!
I want each of you...
to remember...
If you truly believe it's possible...
anyone can fly...
into the endless blue.
I'm sorry you were injured. It's my fault.
You just got lucky. That fall could have been a lot worse.
I'd be mad, but that'd just hurt more.
I promise I won't go to school ever again.
Yeah, about that school stuff...
you just want to attend, right?
Fine, then. I'll cave.
You can both go back to school tomorrow.
I hope you're happy.
Now leave me alone.
Yes, Master. Have a good night.
Good morning! How are you?
Icarus!
Icarus, did you do the math homework?
I did it this morning.
Oh, hey, Nymph!
You like to watch soaps, don't you?
Isn't that nice, Tomo?
Doesn't look like the girls will have any trouble making new friends.
Oh, good.
Haven't you ever seen a birdcage before?
Nymph really likes birds. She knows all of their names.
What the hell did you do that for?
It doesn't really matter.
Whoa, seriously?
That's... a lot.
What are these things, Master?
They're not mine.
They're love letters. Like from boys.
Love letters from boys?
This is just stupid.
Stop it!
Think about the people who poured their hearts out in those letters.
You can't just throw them away!
But that doesn't interest me in the slightest.
Just read them or at least take them home.
Would it kill you to do that?
Geez, Bug, you're so annoying sometimes.
Love letters?
Yeah, you should have seen the pile. There was a freaking ton of them.
But do you really think Icarus can understand the concept of love when it's simply written on a piece of paper?
She said she wants to try to figure it out, which is why she's in the library right now reading each one.
She's keeping them to herself. How sweet of her. If it were me, I'd read them aloud to the entire student body.
Gee. I never knew the guys in our school had such weird fetishes. She has wings, you know? Real wings.
But Icarus has a lot going for her. She's cute and she can cook. And Nymph's cute too, as well as being a cool person.
Yeah, I guess you got a point there.
So what do you think, Tomo?
Don't act like I'm an idiot. You've been living with Icarus this entire time.
Are you saying you haven't once thought she's cute?
See what? You're out of your damn mind.
What an idiot!
Deny all you want, just don't be a dick!
But I hear what you're saying. You don't really like her like her, but you more like her like a friend.
Well, yeah, like a friend. I never like her like her.
Oh, good.
Way to cover, Tomoki.
Tomoki, you are so evil.
Shut up, I am not. I'm just... I'm just happy for both of us.
We're trying to lead normal lives.
If you think about it, they're not that much different from us.
So why shouldn't they have the same chances, you know?
I just hope Icarus can learn how to act more human.
So that maybe, one day, she can learn how to smile.
This is stupid. They're all the same. They keep seeing how much they're in love with you.
If your eyes stay green like that forever, you'll never be able to understand what this love thing they're talking about is.
Huh?
It'll be easier if I just show you.
Good time for it, since there's no one else around to interrupt us.
I've been watching you like a hawk the whole time I've been with you.
Here we go.
Initiating scan.
Functionality protection, 99% normal.
Variable wing protection, 72% normal.
Memory protection, 100%.
Emotional protection, 100%.
I knew something was up.
You've got protections all over you.
Your abilities, your memories, even your emotions.
What a freaking joke.
What?
You're only more than a doll.
You used to be the infamous Uranus Queen who terrorized the entire Synapse.
Am I interrupting?
Not anymore, you're not.
So I don't get it.
If Alpha doesn't know what love is, why is she reading all those idiotic letters?
Kinda silly, don't you think?
I do.
Although it seems as if she's had some restrictions placed on her emotions.
But you're an angeloid yourself and you seem pretty well balanced.
Based on what I've witnessed, I would guess you were both sent here for entirely different purposes.
What are you getting at, nerd bug?
I wonder what these letters mean.
I can read all the words, but they hold no meaning and that bothers me.
Why?
I love you.
What does it mean, master?
What does it mean, Master?
It's beautiful as it will be in the 50th in the 80s.
You're it бег apart, maybe you're beautiful.
You might add clothes back here,
so nothing will этооas will give you Hollywood,
誰も拍手を惜しまないだろう
また会おう いつの日か
君のその顔を 忘れない
ご視聴ありがとうございました
for whom the shooting festival is held.